Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.3.6
Marist College
  Box 1537 - Box 1543
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1541 - Box 1544
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1545 - Box 1548
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1549 - Box 1552
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1553 - Box 1556
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1557 - Box 1560
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1561
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Staff, undated; 1 (Box 1561)
    - Mary Davis, 1
    - Verso: Mary Davis, 1-verso
    - Ann St. Peter, 2
    - Verso: Ann St. Peter, 2-verso
    - [Prosper Buranelli] Verso: For Ann St. Peter from Felicity Buranelli; 6/19/1961, 3
    - Verso: For Ann St. Peter, 3-verso
    - [Prosper Buranelli] Verso: For Electra Nicks from Felicity Buranelli; 6/19/1961, 4
    - Verso: For Electra Nicks from Felicity Buranelli, 4-verso
    - [Prosper Buranelli, right, Lowell Thomas, center], 5
    - [Prosper Buranelli on skis], 6
  - Subject files: Statue of Liberty [early models], undated; 2 (Box 1561)
    - Note: Early models of Statue of Liberty, 1
    - Statue of plaster cas tcolor., 2
    - Verso: Statue of plaster cas tcolor., 2-verso
    - dark (almost black) bronze, 3
    - Verso: dark (almost black) bronze, 3-verso
    - Tree a brilliant red. Statue - black, Flowers in foreground a combination of colors., 4
    - Verso: Tree a brilliant red. Statue - black, Flowers in foreground a combination of colors., 4-verso
    - Grey dress blue collar., 5
    - Verso: Grey dress blue collar., 5-verso
  - Subject files: Don Bennett Steffa, 1958; 3 (Box 1561)
    - This is Ernie Bauman. Among his other accomplishments, he is a ski instructor. If you should ever be interested in virgin ski territory, he can fly you to breathtaking areas. His ski lift is portable and he can provide you with all comforts. Yours, D B Steffa, 1
    - Verso: This is Ernie Bauman. Among his other accomplishments, he is a ski instructor. If you should ever be interested in virgin ski territory, he can fly you to breathtaking areas. His ski lift is portable and he can provide you with all comforts. Yours, D B Steffa, 1-verso
    - [Some sort of chairlift machine], 2
    - [Chairlift machine (?)], 3
    - [Charlift machine (?)], 4
    - [Mechanics of a chairlift (?)], 5
    - Location of wreck, 6
    - Verso: Location of wreck, 6-verso
    - [Man standing in front of an airplane], 7
    - [Man leaning on an airplane], 8
    - [Men next to wrecked airplane], 9
    - [Airplane wreck], 10
    - [Men standing in front of a wrecked airplane], 11
    - [Remains of an airplane crash], 12
    - [Skeleton of an airplane], 13
  - Subject files: Otto Steiner, undated; 4 (Box 1561)
    - On one of my [?] about 1937; Otto Steiner; self portrait, 1
    - Verso: On one of my [?] about 1937; Otto Steiner; self portrait, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Lieutenant S. Claire Streett, undated; 5 (Box 1561)
    - Lt. S. Claire Streett, 1
    - Verso: Lt. S. Claire Streett, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Sun Oil Company, circa 1930s; 6 (Box 1561)
    - [left to right] Westbrook Pegler, Lowell Thomas, Frank Mason, Floyd Gibbons; New York Advertising Club photo made by N.Y. Times studio, 1
    - Verso: [left to right] Westbrook Pegler, Lowell Thomas, Frank Mason, Floyd Gibbons; New York Advertising Club photo made by N.Y. Times studio, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Swimming, 1930s; 7 (Box 1561)
    - [Lowell Thomas in a pool], 1
    - [Inground pool], 2
  - Subject files: Switzerland, undated; 8 (Box 1561)
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man outside of Parsennbahn in Switzerland], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas handing something to a man in front of Parsennbahn in Switzerland], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men standing outside Hotel Parfenn in Switzerland], 3
  - Subject files: Taj Mahal [color photograph], undated; 9 (Box 1561)
    - [Color photograph of the Taj Mahal], 1
  - Subject files: Telegrams [Lowell Thomas receives 266,000 Western Union telegrams], 1934; 10 (Box 1561)
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, Prosper Buranelli, right, (Homer Croy?, left)], 1
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer [includes color photograph], circa 1963 - 1965; 11 (Box 1561)
    - Christle [sic] Thalhammer uses her own Austrian technique at Alta. She is daughter of Kurt Thalammer [sic], one of first Austrian skiers to bring Alpine racing to the United States, 1
    - Verso: Christle [sic] Thalhammer uses her own Austrian technique at Alta. She is daughter of Kurt Thalammer [sic], one of first Austrian skiers to bring Alpine racing to the United States, 1-verso
    - [Christle Thalhammer skiing], 2
    - [Christle Thalhammer skiing], 3
    - [Christle Thalhammer skiing], 4
    - [Christle Thalhammer skiing], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas cleaning his ski boots], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas with Christle Thalhammer and two others], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with Christle Thalhammer and two others], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas with Christle Thalhammer and others skiing], 9
    - [Three people with skiis], 10
    - [Three people with skiis], 11
    - [Skiier going off a cliff], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others in front of an ornate altar], 13
    - Verso: Ali Zaarour, press photographer, Jerusalem - H. K. of Jordan, 13-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others in front of an ornate altar], 14
    - Verso: Ali Zaarour, press photographer, Jerusalem - H. K. of Jordan, 14-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with Joan Trippe], 15
    - Verso: Juan Trippe [center], [Lowell Thomas, right}, 15-verso
    - [Woman in fur coat on plane], 16
    - [Woman in fur coat with hood on plane], 17
    - [Woman and Santa Clause], 18
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer [includes color photographs], circa 1963 - 1965; 12 (Box 1561)
    - Note: From C. W. J. Wallace, Ellinbank, Victoria, Australia [one of nine photographs (12.2-12.10) originally housed in small photographic album], 1
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 2
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 3
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 4
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 5
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 6
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 7
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 8
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 9
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 10
    - [Portrait of Cristl Thalhammer], 11
    - [Portrait of Cristl Thalhammer], 12
    - [Portrait of Cristl Thalhammer], 13
    - [Profile of Christl Thalhammer], 14
    - [Christl Thalhammer in a costume], 15
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 16
    - [Christl Thalhammer in a bathing suit], 17
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 18
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 19
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 20
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 21
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 22
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 23
    - [Christl Thalhammer at a dining table], 24
    - [Christl Thalhammer], 25
    - [Christl Thalhammer and others dancing], 26
    - [Christl Thalhammer ballroom dancing], 27
    - [Christl Thalhammer at a ball], 28
    - [Christl Thalhammer with a Native American], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Christl Thalhammer and a Native American], [3 copies], 30
    - [Christl Thalhammer standing with a Native American], 31
    - [Christl Thalhammer and a Native American], [2 copies], 32
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer, circa 1963 - 1965; 13 (Box 1561)
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to Christl Thalhammer], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer], [2 copies], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer], [2 copies], 4
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 5
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer [includes color photographs], circa 1963 - 1965; 14 (Box 1561)
    - [Painting of Christl Thalhammer], 1
    - [Painting of Christl Thalhammer], 2
    - [Man on a horse], 3
    - [Men at filming location], 4
    - [Man in a turban], 5
    - Neg. 37552 - Marquis Raggis Bird of Paradise (Paradise raggiana Sclater), 6
    - Verso: Neg. 37552 - Marquis Raggis Bird of Paradise (Paradise raggiana Sclater), 6-verso
    - 3. Diyaluma Falls The Photograph show Diyaluma Falls, the highest waterfall in Ceylon and the sixth highest in the world. Diyaluma covers a fall of 570 ft and is one of the most picturesque sights in the hill country of Ceylon., 7
    - Verso: 3. Diyaluma Falls The Photograph show Diyaluma Falls, the highest waterfall in Ceylon and the sixth highest in the world. Diyaluma covers a fall of 570 ft and is one of the most picturesque sights in the hill country of Ceylon., 7-verso
    - 4. The Vatadage The photograph shows the ruins of Vatadage, a circular shrine in Ceylon built in 1196 A.D. Four Buddha figures face the four entrances. The shrine is situated in Polonnaruwa, one of the ancient capitals of Ceylon., 8
    - Verso: 4. The Vatadage The photograph shows the ruins of Vatadage, a circular shrine in Ceylon built in 1196 A.D. Four Buddha figures face the four entrances. The shrine is situated in Polonnaruwa, one of the ancient capitals of Ceylon., 8-verso
    - 1. Sigiriya Rock The photograph show the famous Sigiriya Rock in Ceylon. The massive granite rock, which rises to a height of 600 ft., was converted into a fortress by a King named Kasyapa in the 5th century A.D. The King built a palace, baths, pavilions and a storage tank on the for acres of ground at the summit of the rock. A feature of the Sigiriya Rock is its frescoes which are considered masterpieces of art. The frescoes portray beautiful damsels presumably from King Kasyapa's Court., 9
    - Verso: 1. Sigiriya Rock The photograph show the famous Sigiriya Rock in Ceylon. The massive granite rock, which rises to a height of 600 ft., was converted into a fortress by a King named Kasyapa in the 5th century A.D. The King built a palace, baths, pavilions and a storage tank on the for acres of ground at the summit of the rock. A feature of the Sigiriya Rock is its frescoes which are considered masterpieces of art. The frescoes portray beautiful damsels presumably from King Kasyapa's Court., 9-verso
    - 14. Ceylon Leopard Wild Life in the Ceylon National Parks at Wilpattu and Yala are popular tourist attractions. The picture shows a leopard waiting for its prey in one of the National Parks., 10
    - Verso: 14. Ceylon Leopard Wild Life in the Ceylon National Parks at Wilpattu and Yala are popular tourist attractions. The picture shows a leopard waiting for its prey in one of the National Parks., 10-verso
    - 2. The Ruanvelisaya The photograph show the Ruanvelisaya, a dagoba in Ceylon built in the year 123 B.C. The Ruanvelisaya, is held in special veneration by the Buddhists of Ceylon. Its height is 300 ft. with an equivalent diameter at its base. It was built by Dutugemunu, one of the greatest Kings of ancient Ceylon., 11
    - Verso: 2. The Ruanvelisaya The photograph show the Ruanvelisaya, a dagoba in Ceylon built in the year 123 B.C. The Ruanvelisaya, is held in special veneration by the Buddhists of Ceylon. Its height is 300 ft. with an equivalent diameter at its base. It was built by Dutugemunu, one of the greatest Kings of ancient Ceylon., 11-verso
    - The Bosphorous from Roberts College, Modern age Photographic Service, 12
    - Verso: The Bosphorous from Roberts College, Modern age Photographic Service, 12-verso
    - [The Bosphorous from Roberts College, Modern age Photographic Service], [2 copies], 13
    - "Ram Sat Chatree",Thai Classical Dancing of the -South., 14
    - Verso: "Ram Sat Chatree",Thai Classical Dancing of the -South., 14-verso
    - The Floating Market, 15
    - Verso: The Floating Market, 15-verso
    - At dawn we passed the Temple of the Dawn on our way to "The Floating Market"; Temple of the Dawn, 16
    - Verso: At dawn we passed the Temple of the Dawn on our way to "The Floating Market"; Temple of the Dawn, 16-verso
    - The Elephant Round-Up at Surin Province, 17
    - Verso: The Elephant Round-Up at Surin Province, 17-verso
    - Rajadamnern Avenue, Bangkok, 18
    - Verso: Rajadamnern Avenue, Bangkok, 18-verso
    - Kite Flying at Phramane Ground, Bangkok, 19
    - Verso: Kite Flying at Phramane Ground, Bangkok, 19-verso
    - "Loy Krathong" Festival, 20
    - Verso: "Loy Krathong" Festival, 20-verso
    - Ploughing, 21
    - Verso: Ploughing, 21-verso
    - Buddha Images along the galleries at Wat Po, 22
    - Verso: Buddha Images along the galleries at Wat Po, 22-verso
    - Khao Luang Cave, Petchburi Province, 23
    - Verso: Khao Luang Cave, Petchburi Province, 23-verso
    - Ploughing Ceremony, 24
    - Verso: Ploughing Ceremony, 24-verso
    - The Elephant Round-Up at Surin Province, 25
    - Verso: The Elephant Round-Up at Surin Province, 25-verso
    - Phra Buddha Chai at Saraburi Province, 26
    - Verso: Phra Buddha Chai at Saraburi Province, 26-verso
    - The Royal Barge "Sri Supanahong", 27
    - Verso: The Royal Barge "Sri Supanahong", 27-verso
    - Wat Benjamabopitr (The Marble Temple), 28
    - Verso: Wat Benjamabopitr (The Marble Temple), 28-verso
    - Phra Buddha Badh, Saraburi Province, 29
    - Verso: Phra Buddha Badh, Saraburi Province, 29-verso
    - The Three Pagadas at Lopburi Province, 30
    - Verso: The Three Pagadas at Lopburi Province, 30-verso
    - Chakri Hall in the Grand Palace, 31
    - Verso: Chakri Hall in the Grand Palace, 31-verso
    - Phra Pathom Chedi, Nakorn Pathom Province, 32
    - Verso: Phra Pathom Chedi, Nakorn Pathom Province, 32-verso
    - "KHON", Thai Mask Play, 33
    - Verso: "KHON", Thai Mask Play, 33-verso
    - Temple of the Emerald Buddha, 34
    - Verso: Temple of the Emerald Buddha, 34-verso
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer [includes color photographs], circa 1963 - 1965; 15 (Box 1561)
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][Lowell Thomas standing with a tribesman], 1
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][A crowd of tribespeople], 2
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][A tribal man with a feather headdress], 3
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][Tribal person dressed in grass], 4
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][Tribespeople marching], 5
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][A crowd of tribespeople], 6
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][Tribespeople marching with weapons], 7
    - [very poor quality photographic color prints][Tribespeople with spears], 8
    - [Tribal man in a feather headdress], 9
    - [Christl Thalhammer and a tribesman], 10
    - [Christl Thalhammer standing with two tribesmen], 11
    - [Christl Thalhammer and Lowell Thomas standing with a tribeswoman], 12
    - [Christl Thalhammer standing with three tribesmen], 13
    - [Christl Thalhammer standing with three tribesmen], 14
    - [Christl Thalhammer and Lowell Thomas standing with a tribesman], 15
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer (wedding) [color photographs], circa 1963 - 1965; 16 (Box 1561)
    - Caption: 22. Saptember 1973 [writing in German] [illegible] thanks for your sweet letter. Every body is happy and content, Love She[?] and Manfred[?], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Kurt Thalhammer, right], 2
    - [Christl Talhammer and her husband at their wedding], 3
    - [Christl Thalhammer and her husband holding hands], 4
    - [Christl Thalhammer and her husband cutting their wedding cake], 5
    - [Christl Thalhammer and her husband seated at the altar], 6
    - [Christl Thalhammer and her husband at their wedding ceremony], 7
    - [Christl Thalhammer and her husband], 8
  - Subject files: Christl Thalhammer and Kurt Thalhammer [includes color photographs], circa 1960s - 1970s; 17 (Box 1561)
    - [Kurt Thalhammer and Sig Buchmayr], 1
    - [Kurt Thalhammer and Sig Buchmayr], 2
    - [Kurt Thalhammer and Sig Buchmayr], 3
    - [Christl Thalhammer and a man (her father?) on a ski slope], 4
    - [Christl Thalhammer and three others in the snow (her family?)], 5
    - [Christl Thalhammer with her family(?) holding skis], 6
    - [Christl Thalhammer and her family(?) with ski poles], 7
    - [Christal Thalhammer and her family (?)], 8
    - [Christal Thalhammer with Lowell Thomas and another man on skis], 9
    - [Christal Thalhammer and her family (?) in the snow], 10
    - [It's a aunt[?] of mine [J?]immy, Doudy[?], me and [illegible] his friend Manfred .watching my children playing], 11
    - Verso: It's a aunt[?] of mine [J?]immy, Doudy[?], we [illegible] his friend Manfred .watching my children playing], 11-verso
    - [Christl Thalhammer and a baby (hers?)], 12
    - Michi and Nina my children in our garden., 13
    - Verso: Michi and Nina my children in our garden., 13-verso
    - [Annemarie Proll], 14
  - Subject files: Lowell Thomas Museum (Victor, Colorado) [color photographs], undated; 18 (Box 1561)
    - [The Lowell Thomas Museum in Victor, Colorado], 1
    - [Window of the Lowell Thomas Museum in Victor, Colorado], 2
  - Subject files: Touchdown Club, 1945; 19 (Box 1561)
    - Caption: Touchdown Club - 1945 [some members labeled, Lowell Thomas in center], 1
    - Note: Pic. File What ? Touchdown Club '45, 2
  - Subject files: Travel Hall of Fame, circa 1960s; 20 (Box 1561)
    - Note: November 29, 1973, Dear Mr. Thomas -- Some picture souvenirs of your Travel Hall of Fame experiences in Acapulco [signed] Frank H., Frank Hefter, Director of Public Relations, American Society of Travel Agents, Inc., 1
    - [left to right: Neil Armstrong, Lowell Thomas, Robert Morley, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], 2
    - [left to right: Neil Armstrong, Lowell Thomas, Robert Morley, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], 3
    - [left to right: Neil Armstrong, Lowell Thomas, Robert Morley, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], [3 copies], 4
    - [left to right: Neil Armstrong, Lowell Thomas, Robert Morley, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], 5
    - [left to right: Lowell Thomas, Neil Armstrong, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], [2 copies], 6
    - Verso: L.T. - Neil Armstrong - + George Allen, head of Boeing Aircraft Co., 6-verso
    - [left to right: Lowell Thomas, Neil Armstrong, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], 7
    - [left to right: Lowell Thomas, Neil Armstrong, William M. Allen of the Boeing Corporation], 8
    - Robert Morley in Presidential Suite of Plaza Hyatt, 9
    - Verso: Robert Morley in Presidential Suite of Plaza Hyatt, 9-verso
  - Subject files: Travel Hall of Fame trophy, 1972; 21 (Box 1561)
    - [Travel Hall of Fame trophy], 1
    - Note: [note from the American Society of Travel Agents concerning The Travel Hall of Fame Trophy], 2
  - Subject files: University of Denver, circa 1940s; 22 (Box 1561)
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking at the University of Denver], 1
  - Subject files: University of Denver (Lowell Thomas accepts the Evans Award during Founder's Day ceremony), 1974 March 4; 23 (Box 1561)
    - [Lowell Thomas accepting the Evan Award during the Founder's Day ceremony at the University of Denver], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking at the Founder's Day ceremony at the University of Denver], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas giving a speech at the Founder's Day ceremony at the University of Denver], 3
  - Subject files: U. S. Steel, circa 1950s; 24 (Box 1561)
    - Dr. Edwin M. McMillan; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 1
    - Verso: Dr. Edwin M. McMillan; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 1-verso
    - Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 2
    - Verso: Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 2-verso
    - Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 3
    - Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 4
    - Verso: Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 4-verso
    - Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 5
    - Verso: Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 5-verso
    - Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 6
    - Verso: Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 6-verso
    - Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 7
    - Verso: Bob Kline; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 7-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing by beakers at U.S. Steel], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas standing by beakers at U.S. Steel], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas at U.S. Steel], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas at U.S. Steel], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a machine at U.S. Steel], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas at U.S. Steel], [2 copies], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting on a "Radiation" barrier at U.S. Steel], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas at U.S. Steel], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of people on a roof at U.S. Steel], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a horse], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a horse], 18
    - Rev. Stanley Powell; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 19
    - Verso: Rev. Stanley Powell; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 19-verso
    - Miss Dorothy Smedley; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 20
    - Verso: Miss Dorothy Smedley; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 20-verso
    - Miss Dorothy Smedley; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 21
    - Verso: Miss Dorothy Smedley; Harold Corsini, 933 Penn Ave, Pittsburgh 22, PA, 21-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas reading "Between Planets" by Robert A. Heinlein], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man outside], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in front of the District Library Book Mobile], 24
  Box 1562
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Valparaiso University 100th Commencement [color photographs], 1974 May 19; 1 (Box 1562)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men at the Valparaiso University 100th Commencement ceremony, May 19,1974], 1
  - Subject files: Abigail van Buren ("Dear Abby" ), circa 1970s; 2 (Box 1562)
    - LT and "Dear Abby" at a Washington, D.C. banquet, 1
    - Verso: LT and "Dear Abby" at a Washington, D.C. banquet, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and Abigial van Buren at a dinner event], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Abigail van Buren and another woman], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and Abigail van Buren talking with a woman], 4
  - Subject files: Anna Grace Vester, 1979; 3 (Box 1562)
    - To Lowell Thomas with admiration, Tyler; March 1979; Anna Grace Vester Lind on the roof of the Spafford Children's Center, Old City, Jerusalem; Tyler Wilson Spafford, 1
    - Verso: To Lowell Thomas with admiration, Tyler; March 1979; Anna Grace Vester Lind on the roof of the Spafford Children's Center, Old City, Jerusalem; Tyler Wilson Spafford, 1-verso
  - Bertha Spafford Vester, undated; 4 (Box 1562)
    - Bertha Vester, head of famous American Colony of Jerusalem-and veiled woman in search of relief., 1
    - Verso: Bertha Vester, head of famous American Colony of Jerusalem-and veiled woman in search of relief., 1-verso
    - [Bertha Vester], 2
    - April 4 - 1957; Djamila Payne, 3
    - Verso: April 4 - 1957; Djamila Payne, 3-verso
    - Judges; Grace - Dr. D[?] - Mrs. H [?], 4
    - Verso: Judges; Grace - Dr. D[?] - Mrs. H [?], 4-verso
    - Another view of the judges at work, 5
    - Verso: Another view of the judges at work, 5-verso
    - One of the prize winners, 6
    - Verso: One of the prize winners, 6-verso
    - Dr. D[?] with Maka - Maka was in our children's hospital for over a year, 7
    - Verso: Dr. D[?] with Maka - Maka was in our children's hospital for over a year, 7-verso
    - Part of the crowd., 8
    - Verso: Part of the crowd., 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a group of people], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking at a Rotary International event], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men wearing honarary ribbons], 11
  - Subject files: Bertha Spafford Vester, undated; 5 (Box 1562)
    - [portrait of Bertha Spafford Vester], [many copies], 1
  - Subject files: Bertha Spafford Vester, undated; 6 (Box 1562)
    - [portrait of Bertha Spafford Vester], 1
    - [portrait of Bertha Spafford Vester], [many copies], 2